http://www.stampfinder.com/privacypolicy

:: StampFinder®-The Global Stamp Exchange ::
Online Application Form
Please complete the information form below. (*) Denotes required information.
Fax Number
Investor Services ($225/Year)
Credit Card Number
Expiry Date (MMYY)
*I have read, understand, and agree to your Privacy Policy. and your Terms and Conditions below.
Please Read These Terms and Conditions of Use Carefully Before Using This Site.
By using this site, you signify your consent to the following terms of use. If you do not agree to these terms of use, please do not use the site. We reserve the right, at our discretion, to change, modify, add, or remove portions of these terms at any time. Please check these terms periodically for changes. Your continued use of this site following the posting of changes to these terms means you accept any changes.
RESTRICTIONS ON USE OF MATERIALS.
This site is owned and operated by USID,Inc. (referred to as "USID," "we," "us," or "our" herein). No material (or protion thereof) may be copied, reproduced, republished, downloaded, posted, transmitted, or distributed in any way from this site or any Internet site owned, operated, licensed, or controlled by USID, except that you may download a copy of the materials to any single computer for your personal, noncommercial home use only, provided you keep intact all copyright and other proprietary notices. Modification of the materials or use of the materials for any other purpose is a violation of USID's copyright and other proprietary rights. For purposes of these terms, the use of any such material on any other Internet site or networked computer environment is prohibited. All trademarks, service marks, and trade names are proprietary to USID, Inc.
All images contained on this site are the property of USID, Inc. or its' dealers and are protected by Copyright under the laws of the United States and various other countries. They may not be downloaded or displayed in any manner without the express permission of USID, Inc. All images are digitally marked for identification with unremovable markings detectable by us.
In the event that you download software from the site, the software, including any files, images incorporated in or generated by the software, and data accompanying the software (collectively, the "Software"), are licensed to you by USID. USID does not transfer title to the Software to you. You own the medium on which the Software is recorded, but USID retains full and complete title to the Software itself, and all intellectual property rights therein. You may not redistribute, sell, decompile, reverse-engineer, disassemble, or otherwise reduce the Software to a human-perceivable form.
USE OF CREDIT CARD AND PAYMENT INFORMATION
StampFinder collects your credit card or other payment information in order to help the member dealers process your orders. Dealers are notified of all orders and it is their responsibility to process payments and fulfill orders. StampFinder does not process payment information directly and assumes no responsibility for errors in processing. Any questions regarding payments or orders must be directed to the dealer with whom the order was placed.
LIMITATION OF LIABILITY
StampFinder and the participating dealers make every attempt to provide accurate identification and pricing information. However, neither StampFinder nor the participating dealers shall be held liable for any errors in the identification or pricing of any material offered for sale herein. Proper remedy for any such errors shall be limited to a refund of any amounts paid. Further, StampFinder shall not be held liable for any content contained within the classifieds section or for any content found on sites with links originating from within StampFinder.
NOTE: All information will be kept confidential.
Your name will not be included on any third party mailing lists.
First Name*
Last Name*
Email*
Telephone #
Mailing Address
Country
State
City
Province
Postal Code
Fax Number
Upgrade to Subscribed Member Services ($95/Year)
Sign up for 30 Days Free Trial
ENTER YOUR DEBIT/CREDIT CARD DETAILS*
Cardholder Name
Card Type
Visa
MasterCard
American Express
Diners
Discover
JCB
Credit Card Number
Expiry Date (MMYY)
*I have read, understand, and agree to your Privacy Policy. and your Terms and Conditions below.
Please Read These Terms and Conditions of Use Carefully Before Using This Site.
By using this site, you signify your consent to the following terms of use. If you do not agree to these terms of use, please do not use the site. We reserve the right, at our discretion, to change, modify, add, or remove portions of these terms at any time. Please check these terms periodically for changes. Your continued use of this site following the posting of changes to these terms means you accept any changes.
RESTRICTIONS ON USE OF MATERIALS.
This site is owned and operated by USID,Inc. (referred to as "USID," "we," "us," or "our" herein). No material (or protion thereof) may be copied, reproduced, republished, downloaded, posted, transmitted, or distributed in any way from this site or any Internet site owned, operated, licensed, or controlled by USID, except that you may download a copy of the materials to any single computer for your personal, noncommercial home use only, provided you keep intact all copyright and other proprietary notices. Modification of the materials or use of the materials for any other purpose is a violation of USID's copyright and other proprietary rights. For purposes of these terms, the use of any such material on any other Internet site or networked computer environment is prohibited. All trademarks, service marks, and trade names are proprietary to USID, Inc.
All images contained on this site are the property of USID, Inc. or its' dealers and are protected by Copyright under the laws of the United States and various other countries. They may not be downloaded or displayed in any manner without the express permission of USID, Inc. All images are digitally marked for identification with unremovable markings detectable by us.
In the event that you download software from the site, the software, including any files, images incorporated in or generated by the software, and data accompanying the software (collectively, the "Software"), are licensed to you by USID. USID does not transfer title to the Software to you. You own the medium on which the Software is recorded, but USID retains full and complete title to the Software itself, and all intellectual property rights therein. You may not redistribute, sell, decompile, reverse-engineer, disassemble, or otherwise reduce the Software to a human-perceivable form.
USE OF CREDIT CARD AND PAYMENT INFORMATION
StampFinder collects your credit card or other payment information in order to help the member dealers process your orders. Dealers are notified of all orders and it is their responsibility to process payments and fulfill orders. StampFinder does not process payment information directly and assumes no responsibility for errors in processing. Any questions regarding payments or orders must be directed to the dealer with whom the order was placed.
LIMITATION OF LIABILITY
StampFinder and the participating dealers make every attempt to provide accurate identification and pricing information. However, neither StampFinder nor the participating dealers shall be held liable for any errors in the identification or pricing of any material offered for sale herein. Proper remedy for any such errors shall be limited to a refund of any amounts paid. Further, StampFinder shall not be held liable for any content contained within the classifieds section or for any content found on sites with links originating from within StampFinder.
NOTE: All information will be kept confidential.
Your name will not be included on any third party mailing lists.
Company Name*
First Name*
Last Name
Email ID*
Contact No
Address
Address 2
Country
How and where do you sell stamps today
Subscribed Dealers ($14.99/Month)
Create your own unlimited inventory (at 15 cents per stamp)
Check your inventory against member wants
Send email to members notifying them that you have the stamps they want
Add/Change images to your stamps
Subscribed Auction Houses ($25.99/Month)
Upload the list of your stamps coming up for Auction
Check your inventory against member wants
Send email to members notifying them that you have the stamps they want (50 cents for each notification)
Sign up for 30 Days Free Trial
ENTER YOUR DEBIT/CREDIT CARD DETAILS*
Cardholder Name
Card Type
Visa
MasterCard
American Express
Diners
Discover
JCB
Credit Card Number
Expiry Date (MMYY)
Toggle navigation
Home
View Collections
Investor
Moneystamps Newsletter
The MSR Rating System
Mexico Catalog
Services
Our Commitment To You
Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy, we have provided this statement of policy.
It explains our information collection practices and the choices you can make about the way your information
is collected and used.
-----------------------------------------------------------------
A Special Note About Children
Children are not eligible to use our services without parental supervision, and we ask that minors not submit any personal
information to us. If you are a minor, you can use this service only in conjunction with your parents or guardians permission.
-----------------------------------------------------------------
The Information We Collect:
This privacy policy statement and notice applies to all information collected or submitted on our web site(s).
In our online registration forms and during our telephone registration process, we require you to provide us with information about you.
This includes your full name, full street address, phone number, and your e-mail address. As part of the registration process, we assign
you a personal User ID and password. We consider this ID and password to be your personal information, and treat it as such.
If you place an order for any merchandise that we sell or request a service for which we charge a fee, we may ask that you provide us with
your billing address, shipping address, and credit card information. The credit card information that we may ask you to give us will include
the name of the credit card that you would like us to use, the credit card number, and the card's expiration date. In those circumstances
where we request credit card information, we may use the information that you provide us to verify your name, address and other personal
information in addition to charging your account for the merchandise or services that you buy.
In the course of using our web sites, we may automatically track certain information about you. This information may include the URL that you
just came from (whether this URL is on our site or not), which URL you next go to (whether this URL is on our site or not), what browser you are
using, and your IP address. Note that many other web sites also collect this information automatically.
Please know that we use cookies on our web sites. We use cookies for several purposes, including remembering your log-in information so that
you don't have to enter it on every registered-user page. We also use cookies to build a list of products to track, to keep some of your personal
preferences, and to track new users coming from banner ads so that we can see which ads are most cost effective.
Cookies are stored on your hard drive, not on our web sites. You are always free to decline our cookies if your browser permits, although in
that case declining cookies may prevent our system from tracking items placed in your shopping cart. Declining cookies may also prevent you from
using many of the features that our web sites offer. If you choose to buy or sell on our web sites, we collect information about your buying and selling behavior.
If you choose to post messages on our classifieds or other message areas of our web sites, we may collect such information about you as you choose to disclose.
If you use a third party service made available to you from one of our web sites, or buy merchandise from a third party whose merchandise is offered
on one of our web sites' pages, the third party provider may send us information about you. We also share sufficient information about you with our
dealers so as to allow them to complete any business transaction you may have initiated.
You should check the third party's privacy policy. Regardless
of the third party's privacy policy, please know that any information that we receive from such a third party will be treated by us as if it was received
directly from you, and therefore we will use such information only as described in this privacy policy statement and notice.
If you send us personal correspondence such as e-mails or letters, or if other users or third parties send us correspondence about your activities or
postings on our sites, we may collect such information into a file specific to you.
-----------------------------------------------------------------
The Way We Use Information.
Internally, we use the information that we collect, including personally identifiable information, to improve our marketing and promotional efforts,
to statistically analyze site usage, to improve our content and product offerings, and to enhance our sites' content and layout. We believe these uses
allow us to improve our services and better meet our customers' needs and desires.
We may also use the information that we collect, including personally identifiable information, to deliver information to you that, in some cases, are
targeted to your specific interests. This information may include auction catalogs, notices of auctions which have products that we believe that you will
want to know about, promotions, or information about changes in our policies or procedures. If you do not wish to receive this information and request us
not to send it to you, we will honor your request and remove your name from our lists.
From time to time, we use your e-mail address or other contact information to communicate with you regarding administrative matters or to provide you
with information that we believe that you will want.
If you choose to conduct business with us, we will use your address and other applicable personal information to process your orders, remit to you sales
proceeds, and otherwise service your needs.
We use information in the file we maintain about you, and other information we obtain from your current and past activities on our web sites, to resolve
disputes, troubleshoot problems, and enforce our sales terms and other published policies.
At times, we may look across multiple users to identify problems or resolve disputes. In particular, on rare occasions, we may evaluate your personal
information to look for users using multiple User IDs or aliases, or to enforce our policies.
--------------------------------------------------------
Our Disclosure of Your Information.
We promise never to sell or rent any personally identifiable information about you to any third party without your express permission. However, we may share non-identifying or
aggregate information that does not disclose our customers' identity from time to time with our website designers, dealers, advertisers, or others. For example,
we may tell an advertiser that X number of individuals visited a certain area on one of our websites, or that Y number of men and Z number of women registered with us. Our
Want List Service allows us to share your want list with dealers and by default will not advertise your email. If you respond to an email outside of our system your email may be
shown and we are not responsible for any such use. Users may set specific privacy settings in their member profile.
From time to time we are provided information about someone else (for example, when a buyer asks us to deliver an item to a friend or other third party).
When this occurs, we use the information provided only to complete the applicable order, and do not share this information with outside parties except to
the extent necessary to complete the particular order.
We use return e-mail addresses to answer the e-mail we receive. Such addresses are not shared with outside parties or added to our mailing lists. We may,
however, use such addresses to update our registered user profiles and e-mail address lists.
Unfortunately, due to the existing regulatory environment, we cannot ensure that all of your private communications and other personally identifiable
information will never be disclosed in ways not otherwise described in this notice and privacy policy statement. By way of example (without limiting the
foregoing), we may be forced to disclose information to the government or third parties under certain circumstances, or third parties may unlawfully intercept
or access transmissions or private communications. Further, we can (and you authorize us to) disclose any information about you to law enforcement or other
government officials as we, in our sole discretion, believe necessary or appropriate. Therefore, although we use industry standard practices to protect your
privacy, we do not promise, and you should not expect, that your personally identifiable information or private communications will remain private.
-------------------------------------------------------
Our Commitment To Data Security
To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place what we believe to be appropriate
physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information that we collect about our customers.
-------------------------------------------------------
How You Can Access Or Correct Your Information
You can access all your personally identifiable information that we collect about you by calling or writing us at our corporate offices at the
numbers and addresses provided in the Contact Us section of sites, or by going to the area provided for you to enter and make changes to your
personal information. You can correct factual errors in your personally identifiable information.
To protect your privacy and security, we will take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections, which
may include asking you to provide us with personal information about yourself. In such event, we may record and maintain the information provided in
order to further protect your privacy.
